let questions = [{
    numb: 1,
    question: "Who was the first skater to do a 900 ? ",
    answer: "Tony Hawk",
    options: [
        "Tony Hawk",
        "Danny Way",
        "Eric Koston",
        "Chris Joslin"
    ]
},
{
    numb: 2,
    question: "Where was Skateboarding invented ?",
    answer: "California USA",
    options: [
        "Brazil",
        "California USA",
        "Japan",
        "Netherlands"
    ]
},
{
    numb: 3,
    question: "Which of the options below is a hidden skate rule",
    answer: "Wait for your goddam turn",
    options: [
        "Never eat in the park",
        "Don't smoke in the park",
        "Don't skate mongo",
        "Wait for your goddam turn"
    ]

},
{
    numb: 4,
    question: "What is Tony Hawk Skate style ?",
    answer: "Vert",
    options: [
        "street",
        "Free Style",
        "Vert",
        "Hill Bomb"
    ]
},
{
    numb: 5,
    question: "Who ollied across the Great Wall Of China ?",
    answer: "Danny Way",
    options: [
        "Rodney Mullen",
        "Paul Rodriguez",
        "Sean Malto",
        "Danny Way"
    ]
},
{
    numb: 6,
    question: "Who was the first person to successfully ollie over Wallenberg?",
    answer: "Mark 'The Gonz' Gonzales",
    options: [
        "Mark 'The Gonz' Gonzales",
        "Steve caballero",
        "Tony Alva",
        "Jake Anderson"
    ]
},
{
    numb: 7,
    question: "Which of these skateboarders was the first person to ollie the El Toro High School stairs?",
    answer: "Don Nguyen",
    options: [
        "Dave Baschinsky",
        "Don Nguyen",
        "Ali Boulala",
        "Ryan Decenzo"
    ]
},
{
    numb: 8,
    question: "Which of these is not a form of inline skating?",
    answer: "Cross country",
    options: [
        "Aggressive ",
        "Speed",
        "Cross country",
        "Recreational "
    ]
},
{
    numb: 9,
    question: "Which Skater made the Casper?",
    answer: "Rodney Mullen",
    options: [
        "Tony Hawk",
        "Rodney Mullen",
        "Mike McGill",
        "Alan Gelfand"
    ]
},
{
    numb: 10,
    question: "Which of these skaters was not in Tony Hawks pro skating 3?",
    answer: "Bob Burnquist",
    options: [
        "Rodney Mullen",
        "Tony Hawk",
        "Bob Burnquist",
        "Chad Muska "
    ]
},
]

